What is your job?
お仕事は?
Who do I remember?
私 は誰の姿を思い出すか?
I changed my clothes.
私 は 着 替えた
I know.
私は知っている
I have to get ready for bed.
私 は寝る準備をしないと
yes.
はい
I
私
Do you remember?
は 思い出すか?
Do I remember?
私は思い出すか?
do I remember?
私 は思い出すか?
I have to wear underwear.
私 は下着物を着ないと
私は下着物を着ないと
I have to wear underwear.
Where should I wear it now?
今から履くとこ?
Do you usually wear pajamas?
普段はパジャマ着る?
Are you there?
いる?
Yeah.
うん
Pajamas are nice.
パジャマいいよね
I like the feeling of being defenseless.
無防備の感じがいい
There was no shutting down on New Year's Day either.
元日もシャッティングないところだった
I've almost never seen it.
結局ほぼ見たことない
surely.
確かに
It really suits you, I guess.
めっちゃ似合うね、やっぱ
Look at yourself in the mirror.
鏡で自分で見て
cute.
かわいい
Which one?
どっちが?
pajamas?
パジャマ?
Yeah.
うん
Both are cute though.
どっちもかわいいけどね
My legs are extremely thin.
足がめちゃくちゃ細いじゃん
I'm changing clothes.
着替えてるとこ
I thought it was okay.
いいかなと思ったんですけど
Mari met me online like this,
マリさんはこういうネット上で会って、
Do you sometimes come to the hotel on the same day and do it?
いきなり当日ホテル来て、 たまにやるんですか?
There is none.
無いです
Then you should stop.
じゃあやめたほうがいいですよ
It's better to quit today.
今日最後にやめたほうがいいですよ
Do you have a boyfriend now?
今、彼氏とかいますか?
not present.
いない
not present?
い ない?
want?
欲しい?
I really want it.
やっぱ欲しい
Why do you want it?
なんで欲しいの?
What kind of boyfriend do you not want right now, and when do you want him?
どういう彼、今いないくて、 どういう時欲しいなとか思います?
When I'm alone.
一人の時は
But you live alone, right?
でも結構、一人暮らしでしょ?
So you're lonely all the time?
じゃあずっと寂しいってこと?
surely.
確かに
What do you mean?
ってこと?
What do you want us to do together?
一緒にいて何して欲しいのがあるんですか?
Just being next to each other is enough.
隣り居るだけでいい
Somehow,
なんか、
Oh, well, they don't talk.
あ いつらもまあ、 喋ってくれないじゃないですか
We sleep with our bodies close to each other, just because the dog is sleeping with us.
体くっつけて寝てる、 犬が寝てくれてるだけで、
I guess it calms down or something?
落ち着いたりとかするんじゃないですか?
I do, but he won't talk.
するけど、喋ってくれないから
So, when it comes to emergency, speak, when it comes to emergency, I mean,
じゃあ、いざという時喋って、 いざという時っていうか、
What do you mean?
なんていうの?
He talks sometimes.
時々喋ってくれる
What do you mean?
なんていうの?
Well, I guess people are good.
まあ、人がいいのか
I wonder, is there a type of appearance?
なんだろう、見た目のタイプとかあるんですか?
Wow, really not.
うわ、ほんまにない
kind.
優しい
I'll take a look inside.
中身めっちゃ見ます
I feel like I'm calm when I'm with you.
一緒にいて落ち着くみたいな
It's like being at home together and stress-free.
家で一緒にいてストレスがないみたいな
There are people who tell me that they really love me.
自分のことをめっちゃ好きって言ってくれる人がいる
ah.
あー
Isn't there one?
いるんじゃないですか?
If it's there, I'll return it, but it's there.
いたら返し、いるんですけど
No, but it's kind of like a hurdle.
いや、でもなんかこう、 ハードルっていうか、
I have high ideals.
理想が高い
It's not expensive.
高くないんです
Is it like that with previous generations?
歴代とかもそんな感じですか?
Well, I wasn't told that I was really cool.
あんま、あんまかっこいいって言われなかったですね
Friends and stuff.
友達とか
Hey.
へー
Ah, I see.
あ、そうか
Do you feel like you really chose him based on his personality?
本当に性格で選んでたって感じですか?
Yeah.
うん
I thought it was cool myself.
自分はでもかっこいいと思ってました
Thinking back on it now, do you think it was cool?
今思い出してみて、 かっこよかったって思います?
Oh, because I liked it.
わ、好きだったからですね
Well then, that's what it is.
じゃあ、やっぱそうなんだ
I mean, it's cool if you fall in love with it.
中身っていうか、好きになったらかっこいいって
That's nice.
いいですね
That's it.
それはそれでね
So, I don't care about appearance.
じゃあ、見た目はこだわりないんだ
Isn't there something like this that really appeals to you?
こういうとこにグッとくるとかないですか?
Something like a fetish.
フェチ的なもんとか
It feels like it's coming.
なんかグッとくるみたいな
It's not that I like it or dislike it, I just get a kick out of it.
別に好きとか嫌いとかじゃなく、 ただただグッと来てしまう
Like.
みたい な
For some reason, I feel drawn to it.
なんか、なぜか心惹かれちゃうみたいな
He will help you when you are in trouble.
困ってる時、助けてくれる
But this isn't a fetish.
でも、これフェチじゃないですよね
yes.
そう
It might be more like that.
なんかもっとあれかもしれない
It's like a conditioned reflex.
条件反射みたいな
For example, if a man meets a woman with beautiful feet,
例えば男の人が、 足がきれいな女の人にいたら、
I really like wearing tank tops.
タンクトップ着てるのめっちゃ好きです
I like what I see around here.
ここら辺見えたら好きです
arm?
腕?
But wouldn't it be okay to wear short sleeves?
でも、半袖でもいいんじゃないですか?
Short sleeves are no good.
半袖じゃダメなんですよ
It's nice to have a tank top on and this area is empty.
タンクトップで、ここが空いてるのもいいです
Here?
ここが?
Today, at the station, I saw someone in a tank top carrying a Vuitton bag.
今日、駅で、 ビトンのカバン持ったタンクトップ居て、
I was like, what is this guy?
こいつ何だって感じでしたけど
It didn't make sense though.
意味不明でしたけど
Wear it outside of a tank top.
タンクトップ外で着てて
A little muscle?
ちょっと筋肉?
Yeah.
うん
So what if you were walking around town shirtless?
じゃあ、町で上半身裸で歩いてたら?
Isn't it a little different?
ちょっと違くないですか?
Is it a little different?
ちょっと違うか
Don't you have a muscle fetish?
筋肉フェチでもない?
It's better to have it than not have it.
無いよりあった方がいいな
Spindly?
ひょろひょろ?
Are there people who like pretty androgynous, thin boys?
結構中性的で細い男の子が好きな人とかいろいろあるんですか?
It's better to have it than not have it.
無いよりあった方がいいな
It's okay without it.
無 くてもいい
It's not just a little, it's a little bit like a fetish.
ちょっとじゃなくて、 フェチっぽいところもちょっとある
Do you have a fetish for clothes or tank tops?
服装とか、 タンクトップフェチか
I really like simple.
ほ ん まにシンプルがいいです
A tank top or something white.
タンクトップとか、 白いやつとか
Isn't there a surprising amount of these lately?
最近、意外と多くないですか?
Yeah.
うん
Somehow,
なんか、
It's safe, not particularly fashionable or unique, but
無 難中、別にオシャレ、 個性的じゃないけど、
Do you feel like it's set up?
整った感じ?
Is that what it feels like?
そういう感じ?
I had to change my clothes for a while, but
ちょっと着替えてもらっちゃったんですけど、
This is a complete pajama fetish.
ここが完全なパジャマフェチなんですよ
Isn't it amazing, you have a pajama fetish?
すごくないですか、パジャマフェチ?
For girls, it's a fetish, pajamas, etc.
女の子だと、 フェチというか、 パジャマ、
A girl who likes to collect muscles
筋肉、集めるのが好きな子
Well, I don't have to wear pajamas.
とか、 パジャマも着なくはないですから
Is it difficult to wash?
洗濯大変?
It's hard to wash.
洗濯大変
Is that so?
そう なんですか?
I hated it.
嫌かった
Those made of fabric are easy to care for,
そういう生地のやつが、 手入れも楽だし、
Even if you put it in the washing machine and dryer, it won't wrinkle,
洗濯機で乾燥機入れても、 シワつかんし、
There are people who say things like that.
みたいな言う人いるんですよね
surely.
確かに
Does it feel good to the touch?
手触りいい感じですか?
Fair enough.
まあまあ
Is it ok to the touch?
手触り、まあまあですか?
Fair enough.
まあまあ
It's really good.
めっちゃいいですよ
Isn't there such a thing?
そんなもんない?
There's no such thing.
そんなもんない
That's what it is.
そんなもんですよ
No, I guess so.
いや、そうなんでしょう
It's really good.
めっちゃいいですよ
These pajamas feel so nice to the touch.
こんな手触りいいんですね、パジャマ
Can you feel this area too?
この辺も手触り?
It's good, and this area also feels nice to the touch.
いいし、この辺も手触りいいですね
Not pajamas.
パジャマじゃない
Is this okay?
これは大丈夫?
yes.
はい
This is OK.
これならOKだ
これならOK
this is?
これは?
No.
ダメ
Can I have you stand up for once?
一回立ってみてもらっていいですか?
Is the top okay?
上は大丈夫?
Above.
上は
Not above.
上はじゃない
My hair is curly.
髪がなっている
Is this okay?
これとこ大丈夫?
Yeah.
うん
Behind, behind, behind.
後ろ、後ろ、後ろ
Is this okay?
こっちは大丈夫?
Is everything okay here?
ここは大丈夫?
No, it was amazing.
いや、すごかった
Well, I was just saying that this one is good.
じゃあ、こっちはいいってさっき言ってたんだけど
This one is fine.
こっちはいいんだ
For pajama fetish.
パジャマフェチ的には
It's such a thrill.
めちゃくちゃスリルだよね
It's okay here.
ここは大丈夫なんだ
It's boring here.
ここはくぐったい
Eh, but it's like, huh?
え、でも、うーみたいになるんですね
It's just normal.
普通にくぐったい
Ah, that's good.
あ、いいじゃん
I feel like one piece of cloth is just right.
布1枚ぐらいがちょうどいいって感じだね
Butt, can I have a look at your butt?
お尻、お尻見してもらっていい?
Yeah.
うん
Pajamas are just right.
パジャマだけちょうどいい
Hey, this
ちょっと、これ
That's fine.
だけ でいいじゃん
It's a great defense.
てっぺきな守りですね
Should I not touch it?
触らないでいいのかな?
This is quite amazing.
なかなかだよ、これ
It's tickling.
くすぐってる
Right?
でしょ?
I don't really understand distance.
ちょっと、距離感がわかんない
Wait a minute, this is fine.
ちょっと、でいいじゃん、これ
Did you run away?
逃げた?
It's tickling.
くすぐってる
Does that mean there's a wrong way to touch it?
触り方がいけないってこと?
Yes, absolutely.
うん、絶対そう
I thought this was the most sensitive area, but that's it.
ここ一番敏感かと思ったら、あれなんだよ
It's okay here.
ここ大丈夫なんだよ
Is it coming out?
でてる?
this.
これ
Eh heh.
え へ へ
Ehehe.
えへへ
That's amazing.
すごいよ
It's getting really slimy.
めっちゃヌルヌルになってる
Eh heh.
え へ へ
How do you do it?
どうやってやるの?
picture?
え?
Hurry, sass.
さっさっさっ
Why don't you lie?
なんで、嘘つかないの?
Yeah.
うん
The moment I take my clothes off, they laugh at me and I feel embarrassed.
脱がされた瞬間、笑われて、恥ずかしいんだよ
Eh heh.
え へへ
Here it is.
ここが
When I take it off, it reminds me of my middle school days.
脱がすと、中学時代を思い出しますね
Ehehe.
えへへ
It doesn't tickle, does it?
くすぐったくないでしょ
Aren't you ticklish?
くすぐったくないんですか?
It's not ticklish at all.
全然くすぐったくないですよ
It's not ticklish.
くすぐったくはない
No, isn't it ticklish?
いや、くすぐったいんじゃないんですか?
no.
いや
Well, what can I say, it feels good.
あのー、 なんと言えば、気持ちいいというか
Eh heh.
え へへ
It's not ticklish.
くすぐったくはない
If I did the opposite, you wouldn't be able to say it was amazing.
俺が逆にやったら、めっちゃわーって言えないでしょ
Eh heh.
え へ へ
What, aren't you ticklish?
え、くすぐったくないんですか?
No, it's more ticklish than it feels good.
いや、気持ちいいより、のくすぐったいの
Ehehe.
えへへ
weak point?
苦手?
I don't like myself.
自分嫌だねんの
I'm not good at it, I'm not good at it.
苦手なの、うまくない
It just feels good.
気持ちいいだけですよ
No, look.
いや、ほら
why?
なんで?
Ehehe.
えへへ
I'm running away.
逃げてますよ
I don't like it
嫌だ
That's it.
って
I'm not good at it, so why do I hate it so much?
苦 手なので、なんでこんなに嫌だって
Why do you hate it so much?
なんでこんなに嫌だって
Ehehe.
えへへ
What should I do?
どうしたらいいんですか?
What do you usually do?
いつもどうしてるんですか?
What should I do if my heart is right in front of me?
心臓が目の前にあったらどうしていいんですか?
I don't do anything.
なんもしない
Is there such a thing?
そんなことあるんですか?
for example...
例えば...
To lick or not to lick.
舐めるとか舐めないとか
It's really ultimate.
めっちゃ究極です
Then I won't lick it.
じゃあ舐めないです
It's also possible not to lick it.
舐めないのもありです
That's true.
ありなんだ
There is one thing called licking.
舐めるってのも一つありです
What should I do?
どうしたらいいんですか?
So... lick it.
だから...舐める
lick.
舐める
I'll lick it for now.
とりあえず舐める
Once you lick it...
舐めたらあっという間...
It's not very big.
とてもデカくない
I've never licked it.
舐めたことない
how?
どうやって?
Have you ever licked it?
舐めたことあるんでしょ?
I've never licked it.
舐めたことない
It feels so good.
めっちゃ気持ちいい
Is this okay?
これであってるんですか?
Is it right?
あってます?
It's nothing as long as it feels good.
気持ちよければなんでもない
The back of the face.
顔の裏とか
Is it here?
ここですか?
do not have.
ない
You can tell by the reaction, right?
反応見てわかるでしょ?
I wonder if it feels good.
気持ちいいのかなって
Add it again.
もう一回加えて
It's really powerful when you look at it.
こっち見てくるとめっちゃパワー
The hair on my nose feels good.
鼻に毛が気持ちいい
Please wait.
待って ください
why?
なんで?
Are you laughing?
笑っちゃう?
If you say that much.
そんなに言われたら
Is it okay?
いいっしょ?
I just feel good.
俺、気持ちいいだけだから
different.
違う
Not good.
よくない
Wait, wait a minute.
待って、ちょっと待って
Please wait once.
一回待ってください
Wait, wait.
待って、待って
hang on.
待って
Straddle this way.
このまままたがって
I was sleeping a lot.
めっちゃ寝てた
It's so cold.
めっちゃ寒い
It was intense.
激しくした
The binding is terrible.
縛りがヤバい
Impossible.
無理
My stomach has come out.
お腹出しちゃった